Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 12: Development Office, Fund Raising, and Alumni records, 1843-2016
  - Sub-series 12.12: Alumni financial records, 1874-2004; 2.5 Cubic Feet in five boxes
    - Packer Institute Fund, miscellaneous funding records, 1917 (Box 486, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with donors: miscellaneous, 1917-1919 (Box 486, Folder 2)
    - Alumnae Auxiliary of the Red Cross Treasurer's Report, 1918-1919 (Box 486, Folder 3)
    - Alumnae Association bank account ledgers, 1918-1965 (Box 486, Folder 4)
      National City Bank of New York / The Brooklyn Savings Bank / Kings County Trust Company
    - Alumnae Fund, 1921-1956 (Box 486, Folder 5)
    - Alumnae checkbook, 1924-1926 (Box 486, Folder 6)
    - Alumnae Memorial Scholarship, 1924, 1952 (Box 486, Folder 7)
    - Associate Alumnae Treasurer's Report, 1926-1927 (Box 486, Folder 8)
    - Funds of the Associate Alumnae, 1928 (Box 486, Folder 9)
    - Alumnae checkbook, 1928-1938 (Box 486, Folder 10)
    - Amateur performance of the play "The Ivory Door" royalties, 1930 (Box 486, Folder 11)
    - Alumnae Association ledger class gifts, 1933-1952 (Box 486, Folder 12)
    - Lists of Alumnae gifts and scholarships, circa 1935 (Box 486, Folder 13)
    - Associate Alumnae financial ledger, 1935-1940 (Box 486, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, certificates, reports, miscellaneous funding records, class of 1910, 1935-1961 (Box 487, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Funds and scholarships, circa 1936-1961 (Box 487, Folder 2)
    - Alumni chapter dues, 1941-1956 (Box 487, Folder 3)
    - Associate Alumnae Statement of Receipts and Disbursement, 1948 (Box 487, Folder 4)
    - Associate Alumnae financial ledger, 1941-1948 (Box 487, Folder 5)
    - Centennuial Fund Drive Handbook, 1945 (Box 487, Folder 6)
    - Associate Alumnae general ledger, 1948-1959 (Box 487, Folder 7)
    - Associate Alumnae Building Fund donation, 1949 (Box 487, Folder 8)
      Mrs. Burgess Osterhout
    - Monthly balance ledgers with notes, 1949-1960 (Box 487, Folder 9)
    - Associate Alumnae cash receipts journal, 1948-1959 (Box 487, Folder 10)
    - Associate Alumnae cash disbursements journal, 1948-1959 (Box 487, Folder 11)
    - Annual Fund journal, 1952-1956 (Box 487, Folder 12)
    - Alumnae Fund report and class notes, 1956-1957 (Box 488, Folder 1)
    - Alumnae Fund ledger, 1956-1959 (Box 488, Folder 2)
    - Individual contributions to Alumni Fund by class year, 1956-1968 (Box 540, Folder -)
    - Alumnae Fund ledger, 1959-1963 (Box 488, Folder 3)
    - Alumnae Fund ledger, 1963-1965 (Box 488, Folder 4)
    - Cash balance ledger for various Funds, 1959-1981 (Box 488, Folder 5)
    - Alumnae financial reports, 1961-1962 (Box 488, Folder 6)
    - Summary of Alumnae Fund, 1965 (Box 488, Folder 7)
    - Alumnae Treasurer records, 1965-1981 (Box 488, Folder 8)
    - Alumnae financial documents, 1973 (Box 488, Folder 9)
      Added December 12, 2007
    - Records of checks drawn, 1975-1978 (Box 488, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series 12.13: General alumni files, 1843-2013; 2.5 Cubic Feet in nine boxes
    Arranged chronologically, with alumni clippings placed at the end of the series.
    The sub-series contains an assortment of files relating to Packer alumni, dating from 1843 to 2013. It includes some memorabilia that belonged to alumni which had been donated to Packer.
    - 4 notes about classes of 1843-1853 and 1 ribbon printed with "1853" and "B.F.A." (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Alumnae catalogue, 1847-1899 (Box 535, Folder -)
    - Lists of graduates of 1853, 1854, 1865, circa 1890s (Box 494, Folder 1)
    - Cospi (class of 1870) ledger, 1870-1931 (Box 494, Folder 2)
    - Constitution and by-laws of the Associate Alumnae with class list of 1857, 1871 (Box 494, Folder 3)
    - Marie A. Bond collection of autographs, 1871-1948 (Box 494, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from Alonzo Crittenden to Alumnae Association regarding school's history, 1882 (Box 494, Folder 5)
    - Alumnae, Friends, newspaper Article, 1882-1902 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence to Alumnae Association from (?) Lang, 1887 (Box 494, Folder 6)
    - Class gifts – Alumni gifts, 1887-1945 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence to A.A. Low from Associate Alumnae, 1889 (Box 494, Folder 7)
    - History of the class of 1870, PCI from 1870-1890, circa 1890 (Box 494, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten list of graduating class and their current activities., 1896 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1871 ephemera, 1896-1933 (Box 494, Folder 9)
      Includes 25th reunion poem by Robertine W. Brown, 1896 / invitation from Packer to Jospehine Atkinson, 1908 / wedding invitation from Mr. and Mrs. Charles Asa Buttrick to Josie Atkinson, undated / correspondence from Emma Cook to Annie Atkinson, 1933
    - Class of 1898 alumnae notes and memorabilia of Katharine Sloan Pratt, 1898-1966 (Box 494, Folder 10)
      Includes obituary of Mrs. Adella E. Potter, 1966 / June 1898 commencement program / expenditures through 1938 / newsletter, 1948 / 50th anniversary memorabilia
    - Papers regarding Katharine Sloan Pratt, 1898-1961 (Box 494, Folder 11)
      Includes program from dedication of Katharine Sloan Pratt Hall, 1958 / commencement program, June 1898 / Brooklyn Daily Eagle clipping regarding Pratt's appointment to Packer Board of Trustees, 1935 / speaking notes from party honoring Pratt, 1961 / Class Day program, 1898
    - Class of 1854 alumnae notes, 1898 (Box 494, Folder 12)
    - Constitution of the Packer Alumnae Dramatic Association, 1899-1900 (Box 494, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence from Elizabeth Perry to Bryan H. Smith regarding building funds, 1907 (Box 494, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence from Packer secretary to Charlotte Paddock, 1910 (Box 494, Folder 15)
    - Letter from Mary Halliday to Elizabeth Perry, 1911 (Box 494, Folder 16)
      Gift of David Irving Mead, 1942
    - List of alumnae deaths and dates, circa 1920s (Box 494, Folder 17)
    - Biographies of class of 1890, 1920 (Box 494, Folder 18)
    - Booklet - biography of Frances Gardiner Davenport, class of 1890, with donation letter, circa 1927, 1947 (Box 494, Folder 20)
    - Marion McIlveen (class of 1931) scrapbook pages, 1931-1989, 2007 (Box 494, Folder 19)
      Includes donation letter from George M. McIlveen / original scrapbook pages of "Packer Days" including newspaper clippings, photographs, assorted graduation documents / New York Times obituary dated February 1, 1989 / Photocopies of scrapbook pages regarding later life accomplishments, 1942-1943
    - List of college-bound alumnae, 1935-1940 (Box 494, Folder 21)
    - Items pertaining to Pratt Alumna Elizabeth Goodwin, 1938 (Box 494, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Affairs --Centennial Bulletin, 1945 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1902 notebook, 1945-1953 (Box 494, Folder 23)
      Includes meetings, alumni gatherings
    - Published article by Edith Underwood Conard, class of 1951, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 494, Folder 24)
    - Class lists: 1847-1910, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 494, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence from Mrs. Charles C. Miller (donor) enclosing clipping regarding Class of 1880 honorary tablet, 1955 (Box 494, Folder 30)
      Includes newspaper clipping
    - Published article by Mary Jean Scott, class of 1911, 1957 (Box 494, Folder 25)
    - Helen Ormsbee obituary, 1957 (Box 494, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper clipping regarding Dr. Mary Jean Scott, 1958 (Box 494, Folder 27)
    - Envelope for gift of 1894 memorabilia from Gertrude Roberts Griffiths and daughter, 1959 (Box 494, Folder 28)
      Includes list of names, addresses, number of children of class of 1894 members attending a class party date unknown
    - Draft partial manuscript of Packer history, volume 2, circa 1960s (Box 494, Folder 31)
    - Class of 1925 alumnae notes, 1960 (Box 494, Folder 32)
    - "The Cornell Engineer" article by Delia A. Corkey, May 1960 (Box 494, Folder 33)
      Article titled "New Theories of Color Perception"
    - "Past Here and Present There" by Ottilie G. Boetzkes, class of 1899, 1968-1969 (Box 494, Folder 34)
      Includes correspondence from Alice Chadwick Barnwell regarding class donation
    - Brooklyn Spectator clipping: Martuscello/Hug marriage, 1972 (Box 494, Folder 35)
    - Pearsall family history, "Family Yesteryears," and acknowledgement letter, 1976 (Box 495, Folder 1)
      Gift of Otis Pratt Pearsall, 1979
    - Birthday card from President Carter to Mrs. Elizabeth Hall, circa 1977-1981 (Box 495, Folder 2)
      Gift of Thomas L. Hall, 1981
    - Letter to Harold Van Siclen regarding class of 1916 ring donation, 1980 (Box 495, Folder 3)
    - Letter from Edith Palliser Dill regarding Clara M. Reinecke memorabilia gift, 1982 (Box 495, Folder 4)
      Gift included photo, valedictory address, newspaper articles (not in folder)
    - Correspondence and guide for recent graduates, 1983-1986 (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - Alumnae memories, 1984-1991 (Box 495, Folder 6)
      Includes note "Costs of PCI buildings," their cost, and year acquired
    - Alumnae memories, 1987-1990 (Box 495, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence to Director of Alumni from Rosamund Pauli Philipp regarding class of 1913, 1988 (Box 495, Folder 8)
    - Photograph of Alumni Board, 1990 (Box 495, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from Louise Giordano Biggs to classmates regarding 50th Reunion Luncheon, class of 1942, 1992 (Box 495, Folder 10)
    - Transparent Walls, Poems by Ellen Wilson Batchelor, 1993 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Alumni correspondence and poems, 1994-2000s (Box 495, Folder 11)
    - "Perceptive Winds: from Bergen Beach to the Backwoods Trail" poetry and essays by Edith P. Dill, class of 1945, 1995 (Box 495, Folder 12)
    - Conveyance letter from Helen Creuhern(?), 1998 (Box 495, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence including reminiscences of Jeanne "Nanette" Obreight Wetherell, class of 1936, 2001 (Box 495, Folder 14)
    - Calvin Gooding memorial, class of 1981, 2002-2003 (Box 495, Folder 15)
    - E-mails between Dona Laughlin and Telly Halkias and related article in "The Advocate", 2007 (Box 495, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and promotional materials from Barbara Stolfi-Maggio to Ainka Shackleford regarding published memoir, 2010 (Box 495, Folder 17)
    - Donation in honor of Martha Atwater, 2013 (Box 495, Folder 18)
    - Alumni clippings, A-C, 1929-1970 (Box 495, Folder 19)
      Announcements about individual classmates and their accomplishments and activities. Many clipped and taped to index cards. Includes Presidents of Women's Universities Mary Ingraham Bunting and Phyliss Williams Lehmann.
    - Alumni clippings, D-I, 1910,1945-1975 (Box 495, Folder 20)
      Announcements about individual classmates and their accomplishments and activities. Many clipped and taped to index cards.
    - Alumni clippings, J-N, 1908,1956-1970 (Box 495, Folder 21)
    - Alumni clippings, O-Z, 1928-1970 (Box 495, Folder 22)
    - Alumni clippings, various, 1869,1902-1970 (Box 496, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 12.14: Alumni events, 1861-2016; 2.25 Cubic Feet in eight boxes
    The sub-series contains ephemera and photographs relating to alumni events, dating from 1861 to 2016.
    Files relating to the Alumnae Dramatic Association can be found in Sub-series 8.3: Packer Theater.
    - Christmas Reunion, "The Nations Offerings" (1 program), 1861 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Address to Alumnae Association by President Margaret A.S. Kitchel, 1882 (Box 483, Folder 16)
    - Some Thoughts of the Higher Education of Women. Presidential Address before the Associate Alumnae of the Packer Collegiate Institute (2 pamphlets), 1882 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Packer Alumnae Reunion, 1885 (Box 483, Folder 17)
    - Invitation to 9th annual reunion, 1890 (Box 483, Folder 18)
    - Associate Alumnae event invitations, circa 1890s-1910s (Box 483, Folder 19)
      Shrove Tuesday Tea, Second Mondays, An Afternoon of French Music
    - Old songs: a 19th century reverie for the gift fund, 1891 (Box 483, Folder 20)
    - Associate Alumnae address by James M. Taylor, circa 1892 (Box 483, Folder 21)
    - Tribute to the memory of Dr. Darwin G. Eaton at a reunion, 1895 (Box 34, Folder -)
    - Tribute to the memory of Dr. Darwin G. Eaton at a reunion, 1895 (Box 483, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1886 event, 1896 (Box 483, Folder 23)
    - Associate Alumnae Fifteenth Annual Reunion, 1896 (Box 483, Folder 24)
    - "Procul Adeste" program, 1896 (Box 483, Folder 25)
    - "A Morning with Sir Walter Scott", 1896 (Box 483, Folder 26)
    - Music Circle of the Students' Guild of the Packer Alumnae, 1898 (Box 483, Folder 27)
    - First Annual Reunion of Class of 1898, 1899 (Box 483, Folder 28)
    - Associate Alumnae Christmas Teas, circa 1900s (Box 483, Folder 29)
    - Annual Luncheon of Associate Alumnae, 1900 (Box 483, Folder 30)
    - Annual meeting of the Associate Alumnae, 1900 (Box 483, Folder 31)
    - Alumnae meeting announcement, 1901 (Box 483, Folder 32)
    - Invitation to a talk by Nicholas Murray Butler, circa 1902 (Box 483, Folder 33)
    - Alumnae meeting announcement, 1904 (Box 483, Folder 34)
    - Associate Alumnae address by Mary Woolley, circa 1905 (Box 483, Folder 35)
    - Associate Alumnae program, 1906 (Box 483, Folder 36)
    - Alumnae luncheon menu - Delmonico's, 1906 (Box 483, Folder 37)
    - Associate Alumnae Christmas event, 1907 (Box 483, Folder 38)
    - Alumnae luncheon program, menu, and speech by Margaret Hazard Kitchel, 1908 (Box 483, Folder 39)
    - Packer Associate Alumnae 28th Reunion, 2009 (Box 484, Folder 1)
    - Alumnae event, 1909 (Box 484, Folder 2)
    - Annual luncheon of Associate Alumnae, 1910 (Box 484, Folder 3)
    - Alumnae event, 1912 (Box 484, Folder 4)
    - News clipping of 50th year reunion, 1921 (Box 484, Folder 5)
    - Marion Loder Wagner Golden Anniversary, circa 1930s (Box 484, Folder 6)
      Includes alumnae song lyrics
    - Memorial brochure for William Henry Grant, 1934 (Box 484, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1880 reunion. 10 letters, correspondence received by Frances Mead., 1937 (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Class of 1880 Reunion. 1 speech delivered regarding class of 1880. May 12, 1937 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Class of 1880 reunion. 1 mailing card, 1 envelope, 2 postcards, 3 photographs and 8 negatives. May 12, 1937 (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Memorial service program for R. Huntington Wadman, 1944 (Box 484, Folder 8)
    - Alumnae luncheon, 1954 (Box 484, Folder 9)
    - Class of 1935 Twenty-fifth anniversary, 1960 (Box 484, Folder 10)
    - 84th annual reunion, 1966 (Box 484, Folder 13)
    - Reunion Luncheon April, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Reunion Luncheon April, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 1970s (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Photos (includes class of 1925 and 1926), circa 1970s (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1970-1975 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - 90th annual reunion of the Associate Alumnae, 1972 (Box 484, Folder 14)
    - Associate Alumnae Christmas Party, 1972 (Box 484, Folder 15)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Associate Alumnae reunion, 1975 (Box 484, Folder 11)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1975 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Reunion Luncheon Boca Raton, 1975 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Alumnae Room party photograph, 1977 (Box 484, Folder 16)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Summer, Garden City, 1977 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Summer, 1977 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1977 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Lighthouse Point Yacht Club, March 2, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Reunion Luncheon Friday, April 28, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Long Island, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Deerfield, C.C., P.C.L. Luncheon, March 9, 1979 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1980s (Box 202, Folder 1)
      General, photographs, slides, etc.
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1980 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      Contact sheets
    - Reunion Luncheon, Deerfield, C.C., 1980 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Reunion Luncheon, April 24, 1981 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Reunion Luncheon, "Trial by Jury", 1981 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Reunion Luncheon, PCI La Coquille Club, February 25, 1982 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Reunion Luncheon, April 24, 1982 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial press release and Brooklyn maps, 1983 (Box 484, Folder 12)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1983 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - "Packer Herald" Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 1983 (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - Fiftieth Reunion: Class of 1934, 1984 (Box 484, Folder 17)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1984 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Reunion Luncheon, summer, Palm Beach Gardens JDM Country Club, PGA Boulevard, February 26, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      Prints by Sarah Ross
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1987 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Photograph album: Alumnae luncheon (Deerfield Beach, FL), cocktail party (Vero Beach, FL), and supper at Riomar Bay Yacht Club, 1987-1988 (Box 547, Folder -)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Lois Lowry (paperwork), 1988 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1988 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Reunion Luncheon May, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 19)
      Newsletter and pictures
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1989 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Reunion Luncheon Photograph (includes class of 1945 and 1950), circa 1980s-1990s (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1990s (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1990 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Reunion Luncheon Invitations and Programs, 1990-2001 (Box 484, Folder 18)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1991 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Snapper Inn Oakwood, July, 1991 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1991 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1992 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1992 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1993 (Box 203, Folder 4)
      Includes printed materials, negatives and contact sheets
    - Reunion Luncheon (paperwork), 1993 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1993-1994 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Dinner for Classes 1989-1993, 1994 (Box 484, Folder 19)
    - Reunion Luncheon, at Packer, April 30, 1994 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Reunion Luncheon, 1995 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Westchester, 1995 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Class of 1939 (paperwork), 1995-1996 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - 114th Annual Reunion Luncheon, 1996 (Box 484, Folder 20)
    - 115th Annual Reunion Luncheon, 1997 (Box 484, Folder 21)
    - 116th Annual Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 1998 (Box 484, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Association Career Day for Upper School students, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Lunch, 2001 (Box 484, Folder 24)
    - Reunion Luncheon, Class of 1982, 20th Reunion Flyer, 2002 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Reunion Luncheons, 2002-2006 (Box 484, Folder 25)
    - 126th Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 2008 (Box 484, Folder 26)
    - 128th Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 2010 (Box 484, Folder 27)
    - 30th Reunion - Class of 1982, 2012 (Box 484, Folder 28)
    - 130th Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 2012 (Box 484, Folder 29)
    - 131st Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 2013 (Box 484, Folder 30)
    - 132nd Alumni Reunion Luncheon, 2014 (Box 484, Folder 31)
    - 133rd Alumni Reunion, 2015 (Box 484, Folder 32)
    - 134th Alumni Reunion, 2016 (Box 484, Folder 33)
  - Sub-series 12.15: Alumni Association Geographic Chapters, 1910-1999; 1.7 Cubic Feet in four boxes
    This series contains printed materials relating to geographically organized alumni association chapters, dating from 1910 to 1999. Highlights include the first Founder's Day alumni event in 1911.
    - Chapter development, 1966-1987 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Christmas pageants, 1979-1988 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Christmas parties, 1961-1983 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - College night, 1986-1992 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - First Founder's Day, 1911 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Founder's Day, 1983-1986 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Founder's Day, 1987-1994 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Alma Mater sheet music, 1979 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Alumni – Boston area, 1991-1995 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Alumni – Chicago area, 1993 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Alumni – Maine area, 1994 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Alumni – Maryland area, 1984 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Alumni – New York City area, 1986-1997 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Alumni – Ohio area, 1995 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Alumni – Philadelphia area, 1995 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Alumni – Phoenix area, 1997-1999 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Alumni – Vermont area, 1987-1992 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Alumni – Washington, DC area, 1985-1996 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Board member duties, 1962-1989 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - By-laws, 1956-1988 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Entry and departure dates, circa 1990s (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Gifts, 1993-1994 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Nominating committee, 1985-1986 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Career day, 1984 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Career day, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut Chapter Luncheon, 1982 or 1983 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Delaware Valley Chapter, Fall, 1983 (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - D.C. Cocktail Party, March 9, 1985 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Deerfield Beach, February 1, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Rioma Bay Yacht Club, March 9, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - Denver, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - Reunions, 1993-1994 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - Long Island, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Annual Group Thank You Party, May 1, 1994 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Senior Breakfast, 1994-1995 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Pumpkin Patch, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Luncheon, California, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Florida, 1988-1995 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Butterfly Farm, P.C.I. Vermont, 1920-1925 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Paul D. Schafer Memorial Service and Gifts, May 1, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Memorial Garden, 1985 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Sesquicentennial Awards, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Alumnae Association - Montclair chapter, 1910-1955 (Box 489, Folder 4)
    - Alumnae Association - Montclair chapter, 1931-1957 (Box 489, Folder 5)
  - Sub-series 12.16: Alumni Student Relations, 1995-2009; 0.35 Cubic Feet in eleven folders
    The sub-series contains correspondence between current students and alumni, dating from 1995 to 2009. It predominantly contains Valentine's Day card exchanges.
    - Valentine's Day, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Valentine's Day, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Valentine's Day, 1997 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Valentine's Day, 1998 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Valentine's Day, 1999 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Valentine's Day, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Valentine's Day, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Valentine's Day, 2002-2003 (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Valentine's Day, 2004-2009 (Box 489, Folder 2)
    - Young alums - Garden project, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Young alums - Pippin, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 12.17: Alumni directories, 1991-2014; 0.5 Cubic Feet in six folders
    The sub-series contains alumni directories, dating from 1991 to 2014.
    - Alumni Directory, 1991 (Box 496, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Directory, 1996 (Box 496, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Directory, 2000 (Box 496, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Directory, 2005 (Box 497, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Directory, 2014 (Box 497, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Directory CD-ROM, 2014 (Box 554, Folder 6)